Guide to the Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
7456
2660 v., comprising 37.6 cubic ft.
Novels.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Erotic and pornographic novels on gay men's subjects, including such themes as muscle, cowboy, sado-masochism, sailors, and leather, and occurring in such series as Parisian Press, Blueboy Library, Greenleaf, HIS 69, and many others.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Erotic and pornographic novels on gay men's subjects, including such themes as muscle, cowboy, sado-masochism, sailors, and leather, and occurring in such series as Parisian Press, Blueboy Library, Greenleaf, HIS 69, and many others.
SUBJECTS
Subjects:
Gays.; Popular literature.
Form and Genre Terms:
Erotica.; Pornography.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Books are listed alphabetically by author. Title, publisher, series and series number if applicable (-0- if not), and date are also given.
CONTAINER LIST
- Ackworth, Robert C., The Moments Between, Hillman Books, 129, 1959 (Box 33)
- Adam, Daniel, Daddy's Boy, Surree Ltd, SS 030, 1976 (Box 85)
- Adcock, Ron, 17 X 9, Surrey House, HIS 06954, 1973 (Box 70)
- Adler, Hiddy, The Bisexual Boy, Utopia Publications, PP 147, 1975 (Box 88)
- Agazanian, Leo, Confessions Of The Perfect Stud, Phenix Publishers, LL 787, 1968 (Box 44)
- Ahern, John, The Search, Oasis, FGL 12, 1969 (Box 38)
- Albert, Lon, Hours, Universal, A 507S, 1969 (Box 88)
- Alcock, Richard, Campus Rendezvous, Blueboy Library, BB 115, 1978 (Box 11)
- Alcock, Richard, Hot Rod, Blueboy Library, BB 124, 1978 (Box 11)
- Alcock, Richard, Come Again, Surree Ltd, SS 046, 1978 (Box 85)
- Aldyne, Nathan, Vermilion, Avon, 0-380-76596-9-225, 1980 (Box 4)
- Allen, Dave, Hot Tip, Grand Prix Classics, -0-, n.d. (Box 19)
- Allen, Dave, Sea Food For Joe, Grand Prix Classics, -0-, n.d. (Box 19)
- Allen, Dave, Schoolboys In Love, Grand Prix Classics, -0-, n.d. (Box 90)
- Allen, Nick, Dynasty Of Decadence, Brandon House, 999, 1966 (Box 12)
- Allyson, Kym, Daisies In A Chain, Brandon House, 6082, 1969 (Box 13)
- Allyson, Kym, The Queer Letters, Brandon House, 6119, 1970 (Box 13)
- Allyson, Kym, His Male Lover, Lambda Press, LB 108, 1970 (Box 34)
- Allyson, Kym, Boy-Watcher, Phenix Publishers, PR 269, 1970 (Box 45)
- Allyson, Kym, Mansion Of Men, Triumph, TNC 327, 1968 (Box 87)
- Allyson, Kym, You're a Hard Man, Jamie Coxman, Brandon House, 3064, 1969 (Box 90)
- Alpert, Jay, Balls Afire!, Surrey House, MH 428, 1973 (Box 81)
- Alpert, Jay, Put It In! *, Surrey House, MH 451, 1974 (Box 82)
- Alpert, Jay C., Ah Buddies, Surrey House, HIS 06901, 1971 (Box 69)
- Amory, Richard, Song Of The Loon, Greenleaf Classics, GC 213, 1966 (Box 24)
- Amory, Richard, Song Of Aaron, Greenleaf Classics, GC 222, 1967 (Box 24)
- Amory, Richard, Listen, The Loon Sings, Greenleaf Classics, GC 284, 1968 (Box 24)
- Amory, Richard, Fruit Of The Loon, Greenleaf Classics, GC 307, 1968 (Box 24)
- Amory, Richard, Naked On Main Street, Greenleaf Classics, GL 117, 1969 (Box 25)
- Amory, Richard, A Handsome Young Man With Class, Greenleaf Classics, GL 143, 1969 (Box 26)
- Amory, Richard, Longhorn Drive, Greenleaf Classics, GL 146, 1969 (Box 26)
- Amory, Richard, Frost, Olympia Press, -0-, 1971 (Box 38)
- Amory, Richard, Frost, Olympia Press, TC-510, 1971 (Box 39)
- Amory, Richard, Song Of The Loon, Tallis Press, -0-, 1969 (Box 89)
- Anderson, John, 12 Inches, Arena, DS 112, 1982 (Box 1)
- Anderson, John, High School Hunk, Arena, DS 116, 1982 (Box 1)
- Anderson, Max, The Bunghole Boys, Valley Circle Pubn., SV 104, 1971 (Box 88)
- Anderson, Ronnie, Only The Weak Cry, Guild Press Ltd., TC111, 1969 (Box 28)
- Anderson, Ronnie, Hi-Ho The Cherry-O, Guild Press Ltd., TC117, 1969 (Box 28)
- Anderson, Ronnie, Newcocks, Guild Press Ltd., TC116, 1969 (Box 90)
- Anderson, Steven, Cherry Action, Arena, MP 155, 1985 (Box 3)
- Anderson, Steven, Action On The Street, Arena, MP 161, 1986 (Box 3)
- Anderson, Todd, Big Blond And Butch, Arena, MP 117, 1984 (Box 3)
- Andrews, Joe, Strokin' It, Eros Publishing, GYP 103, 1981 (Box 16)
- Andrews, Terry, Rough Trade Italian Style, 101 Enterprises, 101-8, 1968 (Box 39)
- Andrews, Teryl, Flower Boy, 101 Enterprises, 101-11, 1968 (Box 40)
- Andrews, Teryl, Pageboys *, 101 Enterprises, 101-19, 1968 (Box 40)
- Andrews, Teryl, Up And Coming, Phenix Publishers, PR 230, 1969 (Box 44)
- Andrews, Teryl, The Only Way To Fly!, Phenix Publishers, PR 250, 1970 (Box 45)
- Andrews, Teryl, Flight Sixty-Nine, Taurus Publications Inc., 66-233, 1970 (Box 87)
- Andros, Phil, Stud Volume One, Beaumont Classics, -0-, n.d. (Box 6)
- Andros, Phil, Stud Volume Three, Beaumont Classics, -0-, n.d. (Box 6)
- Andros, Phil, San Francisco Hustler, Gay Parisian Press, GPP 106, 1970 (Box 19)
- Andros, Phil, When In Rome Do..., Gay Parisian Press, GP, 1971 (Box 19)
- Andros, Phil, The Joy Spot, Oasis, FGL 13, n.d. (Box 38)
- Anfuss, C. K., The Cocky Cowboy, Rough Trade, RT 414, n.d. (Box 54)
- Anonymous, Us, Bantam Books, 0-553-10141-2, 1973 (Box 5)
- Anonymous, The Daughter Of Fanny Hill, Brandon House, 1024, 1966 (Box 12)
- Anonymous, The Daughter Of Fanny Hill Vol. 2, Brandon House, 2054, 1968 (Box 12)
- Anonymous, The Son Of Fanny Hill, Brandon House, 6121, 1970 (Box 13)
- Anonymous, Rub The Man Down, Centaur Pubns., -0-, 1970 (Box 13)
- Anonymous, S And M Men, Centaur Pubns., -0-, 1970 (Box 13)
- Anonymous, Train Station Sex, Centaur Pubns., -0-, 1970 (Box 13)
- Anonymous, A Boy's First Experiences, Centaur Pubns., -0-, 1970 (Box 13)
- Anonymous, Only A Boy, Collectors Publications, -0-, 1967 (Box 14)
- Anonymous, Male Photographs, Collectors Publications, -0-, 1968 (Box 14)
- Anonymous, Intimate Diaries Of Homosexual Genuises, Echelon, IL-231, 1967 (Box 15)
- Anonymous, The Autobiography Of A Flea, Greenleaf Classics, GC 227, 1967 (Box 24)
- Anonymous, The Tijuana Bible Reader, Greenleaf Classics, GL 101, 1969 (Box 25)
- Anonymous, Friar Peck And His Tale, Greenleaf Classics, GL 113, 1969 (Box 25)
- Anonymous, The Second Tijuana Bible Reader, Greenleaf Classics, GL 133, 1969 (Box 26)
- Anonymous, 7 In A Barn, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, A Crack In The Wall, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, A Night In The Hayloft, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, A Night To Remember, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, Angelo, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, Back Door Love Thrills, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, Bail Out!, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, Boxing Camp, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, Buddy, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, Cock Crazy Cowboy, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, East Ardmore, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, Gang Bang, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, I Found What I Wanted, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, Ken Babcock's Cherry, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, On The Farm In Old Missouri, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, Our New Friend, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, Porthole Buddies, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, San Diego Sailor, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, The Adventures Of Edward, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, The Boys Of Muscle Beach, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, The First Job, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, The Hitch-Hiker, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, The Lifeguard, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, The Team, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, Under The Bridge, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, Weekend Orgy, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, 2 Boys + Teacher = Orgy, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1970 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, After Hours Give It Away!, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1970 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, Queen Of The Road, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1966 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, My First Time Vol 1, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, My First Time Vol 2, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1969 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, Marine Stud, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1971 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, A Night In The Hayloft, Guild Press Ltd., LS-2, 1971 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, Another Night To Remember!!, Guild Press Ltd., LS-3, 1971 (Box 27)
- Anonymous, Size Queen, Homosexual Classics, -0-, n.d. (Box 33)
- Anonymous, Male Bride, Kozy Books, Inc., K 184, 1963 (Box 33)
- Anonymous, When Men Meet, Kozy Books, Inc., K 191, 1963 (Box 33)
- Anonymous, Diary Of A Homosexual, L.S. Publications, IMP 736, 1965 (Box 34)
- Anonymous, Pleasure Punk, LB, LB 101, n.d. (Box 34)
- Anonymous, Bath House Slave, LeSalon, -0-, n.d. (Box 34)
- Anonymous, Teen-Age Stud, Mano Line, Mano Ser. 101, n.d. (Box 36)
- Anonymous, My Son...My Lover, P. E. C., G-1100, 1965 (Box 53)
- Anonymous, Gay Incest:Brotherly Love & Uncontrolled...., Proctor File Illus., PF-1014, n.d. (Box 49)
- Anonymous, Oralmania: Hard Muscles..., Proctor File Illus., PF-1015, n.d. (Box 49)
- Anonymous, Teen Boys: Willing Boys....., Proctor File Illus., PF-1016, n.d. (Box 49)
- Anonymous, Jockstrap, Rough Trade, RT 485, 1980 (Box 56)
- Anonymous, Booted Master, Rough Trade, RT 486, 1980 (Box 56)
- Anonymous, Chicken Hawk, Rough Trade, RT 487, 1980 (Box 56)
- Anonymous, Stable Boy, Rough Trade, RT 488, 1980 (Box 56)
- Anonymous, Hard Leather, Rough Trade, RT 489, 1980 (Box 56)
- Anonymous, Cowpoke, Rough Trade, RT 490, 1980 (Box 56)
- Anonymous, Meat Rack, Rough Trade, RT 491, 1980 (Box 56)
- Anonymous, Marine Master, Rough Trade, RT 492, 1980 (Box 56)
- Anonymous, Coach's Jocks, Rough Trade, RT 494, 1981 (Box 56)
- Anonymous, Hardhat Dude, Rough Trade, RT 496, 1981 (Box 56)
- Anonymous, Brutal Seaman, Rough Trade, RT 497, 1981 (Box 56)
- Anonymous, Tattoo Master, Rough Trade, RT 499, 1981 (Box 56)
- Anonymous, Big Rig Rapist, Rough Trade, RT 501, 1981 (Box 56)
- Anonymous, Sex Toy, Rough Trade, RT 502, 1981 (Box 56)
- Anonymous, Dominant Drill Sergeant, Rough Trade, RT 503, 1981 (Box 56)
- Anonymous, Convict Jungle, Rough Trade, RT 504, 1981 (Box 56)
- Anonymous, Leather Boot Camp, Rough Trade, RT 515, 1982 (Box 57)
- Anonymous, Lifeguard Lust, Rough Trade, RT 516, 1982 (Box 57)
- Anonymous, Hard Hat Chicken, Rough Trade, RT 517, 1982 (Box 57)
- Anonymous, Backwoods Bruisers, Rough Trade, RT 519, 1982 (Box 57)
- Anonymous, Street Corner Meat, Rough Trade, RT 523, 1982 (Box 57)
- Anonymous, Brute Woodsman, Rough Trade, RT 524, 1982 (Box 57)
- Anonymous, Top Kick, Rough Trade, RT 528, 1983 (Box 57)
- Anonymous, Muscle Beach Brutes, Rough Trade, RT 542, 1984 (Box 57)
- Anonymous, Hot Hose Firehouse, Rough Trade, RT 567, 1985 (Box 57)
- Anonymous, Hard Dirty Truckers, Rough Trade, RT 578, 1986 (Box 57)
- Anonymous, Boy-Bait, Rough Trade, RT 607, 1987 (Box 57)
- Anonymous, Hard Hot & Hung, Rough Trade, RT 608, 1987 (Box 57)
- Anonymous, Little Boy Homo Come Blow Your Horn,, Special Publication, -0-, n.d. (Box 58)
- Anonymous, The Male Brothel, Special Publication, -0-, n.d. (Box 58)
- Anonymous, His Black Boyfriend, Star Dist., BB-123, 1986 (Box 58)
- Anonymous, Bucking Broncos, Star Dist., BB-145, 1987 (Box 58)
- Anonymous, Beach Boy, Star Dist., BB-149, 1987 (Box 58)
- Anonymous, Hot Surfer Bums, Star Dist., BB-150, 1987 (Box 58)
- Anonymous, Rick's Big One, Star Dist., BB-153, 1987 (Box 58)
- Anonymous, Farmboy Fun, Star Dist., BB-155, 1987 (Box 58)
- Anonymous, Saigon Memoirs, Star Dist., BB-156, 1987 (Box 58)
- Anonymous, Nazi Sadist, Star Dist., CB-101, 1982 (Box 59)
- Anonymous, French Trench, Star Dist., CB-102, 1982 (Box 59)
- Anonymous, Big Black Sgt., Star Dist., CB-114, 1983 (Box 59)
- Anonymous, Nazi Lust, Star Dist., CB-121, 1983 (Box 59)
- Anonymous, Boot Slave, Star Dist., CB-130, 1984 (Box 59)
- Anonymous, Stud Terror Squad, Star Dist., CB-137, 1984 (Box 59)
- Anonymous, Well-Hung Hustler, Star Dist., fin-01, 1980 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Campus Cock, Star Dist., fin-02, 1980 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Come Hungry, Star Dist., fin-04, 1980 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Beach Bum, Star Dist., fin-05, 1980 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Cycle Stud, Star Dist., fin-06, 1980 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Frisco Cowboy, Star Dist., fin-07, 1980 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Beach Boy, Star Dist., fin-09, 1980 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Leather Hustler, Star Dist., fin-10, 1980 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Back Room Action, Star Dist., fin-11, 1980 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Behind Bars, Star Dist., fin-12, 1980 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Leather Sadist, Star Dist., fin-13, 1980 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Hot Stallions, Star Dist., fin-14, 1980 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Hard Ball, Star Dist., fin-15, 1980 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Rock Hard, Star Dist., fin-17, 1981 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Tight End, Star Dist., fin-19, 1981 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Initiation Night, Star Dist., fin-20, 1981 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Male Clinic, Star Dist., fin-23, 1981 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Firehouse Sex, Star Dist., fin-25, 1981 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Whipmaster, Star Dist., fin-26, 1981 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Navy Studs, Star Dist., fin-29, 1982 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Bath House Bondage, Star Dist., fin-31, 1982 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Hard Men, Star Dist., fin, 1982 (Box 60)
- Anonymous, Leather Lust, Star Dist., fin-32, 1982 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Gym Orgy, Star Dist., fin-33, 1982 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Gym Dominators, Star Dist., fin-38, 1982 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Punished Punks, Star Dist., fin-40, 1982 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Jock Strap, Star Dist., fin-45, 1982 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Meat Rack, Star Dist., fin-47, 1982 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Bike Boy, Star Dist., fin-48, 1982 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Hardcore Hustler, Star Dist., fin-52, 1983 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, High School Quarterback, Star Dist., fin-55, 1983 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Lockerroom Hump, Star Dist., fin-57, 1983 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Beach Boy Stud, Star Dist., fin-58, 1983 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Loving Roommates, Star Dist., fin-61, 1983 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Hard-Driving Man, Star Dist., fin-63, 1983 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Teacher's Bad Boy, Star Dist., fin-65, 1984 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Camp Counselor's Kid, Star Dist., fin-66, 1984 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Frat Night Initiation, Star Dist., fin-67, 1984 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Lockerroom Orgy, Star Dist., fin-69, 1984 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, High School Lovers, Star Dist., fin-72, 1984 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, The Boys From, Kappa Sig, Star Dist., fin-89, 1985 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Coming Out, Star Dist., fin-93, 1985 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Come-Hungry Cruiser, Star Dist., fin-132, 1987 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Boys In Love, Star Dist., fin-139, 1987 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Skateboard Hunk, Star Dist., fin-141, 1987 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Sigma Chi Studs, Star Dist., fin-143, 1987 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Muscle Brute, Star Dist., fin-144, 1987 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Brother Love, Star Dist., GI 110, 1987 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Home, Sex, Home, Star Dist., GI 118, 1987 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Bondage Boys, Star Dist., GI 120, 1987 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Daddy's Training Program, Star Dist., GI 121, 1987 (Box 61)
- Anonymous, Center Court Ballbuster, Star Dist., JS 107, 1985 (Box 62)
- Anonymous, Gym Orgy, Star Dist., JS 122, 1986 (Box 62)
- Anonymous, Brothers At Sea, Star Dist., GI 122, 1987 (Box 62)
- Anonymous, Backyard Twins, Star Dist., GI 123, 1987 (Box 62)
- Anonymous, Slave To His Brother, Star Dist., GI 124, 1987 (Box 62)
- Anonymous, Uncle Jack's Funhouse, Star Dist., GI 126, 1988 (Box 62)
- Anonymous, Breaking Into Leather, Star Dist., MPI 106, 1979 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Big Black Buck, Star Dist., MPI 108, 1979 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Black Sadist, Star Dist., MPI 110, 1979 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Cruise Alley, Star Dist., MPI 111, 1979 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Captive Punk, Star Dist., MPI 113, 1979 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Hard Hat, Star Dist., NM-001, 1979 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Street Hustler, Star Dist., NM-002, 1979 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Leather Whipper, Star Dist., NM-003, 1979 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Kansas City Roper, Star Dist., NM-005, 1980 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Master Sergeant, Star Dist., NM-007, 1980 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Street Trade, Star Dist., NM-008, 1980 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Convict, Star Dist., NM-009, 1980 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Dockside, Star Dist., NM-010, 1980 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Raw Recruit, Star Dist., NM-012, 1980 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Strapped, Star Dist., NM-013, 1980 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Muscle Beach, Star Dist., MB 01, 1981 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Stud Squad, Star Dist., MB 11, 1982 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Bondage Boys, Star Dist., MB 14, 1982 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Best Friends, Star Dist., MDB 03, 1983 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, First Time Trick, Star Dist., MDB 03, 1983 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, A Loving Son, Star Dist., MDB 04, 1983 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, High School Jock, Star Dist., MDB 04, 1983 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Swimteam Stud, Star Dist., JS 127, 1986 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Ball Handler, Star Dist., JS 141, 1987 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Quarterback's Secret Lust, Star Dist., JS 142, 1987 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Track Meat, Star Dist., JS 143, 1987 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Hot Cock, Star Dist., JS 144, 1987 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Bar Room Ball, Star Dist., JS 146, 1987 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Batting His Balls, Star Dist., JS 149, 1988 (Box 63)
- Anonymous, Fast Track, Star Dist., NM-014, 1980 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Basic Training, Star Dist., NM-016, 1980 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Dock Worker, Star Dist., NM-018, 1980 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Cowboy Cock, Star Dist., NM-019, 1980 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Hot Cock, Star Dist., NM-021, 1981 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Leather Drifter, Star Dist., NM-022, 1981 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Seafood, Star Dist., NM-023, 1981 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Naked Cowboy, Star Dist., NM-024, 1981 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Stud Model, Star Dist., NM-025, 1981 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Dad's Discipline, Star Dist., NM-027, 1981 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Quarterback Lover, Star Dist., NM-028, 1981 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Master Mechanic, Star Dist., NM-029, 1981 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Gas Jockey, Star Dist., NM-035, 1981 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Street Punk *, Star Dist., NM-036, 1981 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Hell's Hardhats, Star Dist., NM-047, 1982 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Fraternity Brother, Star Dist., NM-057, 1983 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Army Buddy, Star Dist., NM-058, 1983 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Trucker's Boy, Star Dist., NM-059, 1983 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Coming Out, Star Dist., NM-061, 1983 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Daddy's Boy, Star Dist., NM-062, 1983 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Sonny Boy, Star Dist., NM-064, 1983 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, West Coast Stud, Star Dist., NM-065, 1983 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Freshman Class Virgin, Star Dist., NM-077, 1984 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Black Punk Hustler, Star Dist., NM-079, 1984 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Freshman Class Sissy, Star Dist., NM-083, 1984 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Prep School Nights, Star Dist., NM-087, 1984 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Shore Leave, Star Dist., NM-098, 1985 (Box 64)
- Anonymous, I Like It Rough, Star Dist., NM-142, n.d. (Box 64)
- Anonymous, Highway Stud, Star Dist., NSS 103, 1979 (Box 65)
- Anonymous, Bootlicker, Star Dist., NSS 104, 1979 (Box 65)
- Anonymous, Doing It To David, Star Dist., NM-146, 1987 (Box 65)
- Anonymous, Big Man On Campus, Star Dist., NM-147, 1987 (Box 65)
- Anonymous, Strapped!, Star Dist., NM-148, 1987 (Box 65)
- Anonymous, Fine Firm Buns, Star Dist., NM-150, 1987 (Box 65)
- Anonymous, Wall Street Stud, Star Dist., YS-101, 1987 (Box 67)
- Anonymous, Muscle Beach, Star Dist., YS-104, 1987 (Box 67)
- Anonymous, Rock Group Roadie, Star Dist., YS-105, 1987 (Box 67)
- Anonymous, Hard Traveller, Star Dist., YS-107, 1987 (Box 67)
- Anonymous, Boiler Room Boys, Star Dist., YS-108, 1987 (Box 67)
- Anonymous, Punished Punks, Star Dist., YS-116, 1988 (Box 67)
- Anonymous, Dormitory Boy, Star Dist., YS-120, 1988 (Box 67)
- Anonymous, Homo Road, Twi-World Publications, TWI-19, 1968 (Box 89)
- Anonymous, His Abnormal Love, unknown, M-100, n.d. (Box 89)
- Anonymous, That Gay Bar, unknown, M-102, n.d. (Box 89)
- Anonymous, All The Sad Young Men, Wisdom House, W 108, 1962 (Box 88)
- Anonymous, Angelo, Centaur Publications, -0-, 1970 (Box 92)
- Anonymous, Beach Brute, Star Distributors, fin-77, 1984 (Box 92)
- Anonymous, Boots, Leather, Bikes, Star Distributors Ltd., fin-18, 1981 (Box 92)
- Anonymous, Bruite Biker, Star Distributors Ltd., NM-32, 1981 (Box 92)
- Anonymous, Chosen Society, Twi-World Publications, TWI-20, 1968 (Box 92)
- Anonymous, The Different and the Damned, Publishers Export Co., Special 19, 1968 (Box 92)
- Anonymous, Dock Boys, Star Distributors Ltd., NM-34, 1981 (Box 92)
- Anonymous, Hard Hat Dude, Star Distributors Ltd., RT-496, 1981 (Box 92)
- Anonymous, Hard Hat Hard-Ons, Star Distributors Ltd., RT-569, 1985 (Box 92)
- Anonymous, Hard Time, Star Distributors Ltd., RT-555, 1984 (Box 93)
- Anonymous, Leather Cycle Club, Star Distributors Ltd., RT-493, 1981 (Box 93)
- Anonymous, Nazi Slaves, Star Distributors, CB-134, 1984 (Box 93)
- Anonymous, Orgy Garage, Star Distributors, NM-54, 1982 (Box 93)
- Anonymous, Park Patrol, Star Distributors, MPI-107, 1979 (Box 93)
- Anonymous, A Secret Life, Masquerade Books Inc., 17-2, 1992 (Box 93)
- Anonymous, The Skipper's Slaves, Star Distributors, RT-507, 1982 (Box 93)
- Anonymous, Marine Studs, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 93)
- Anonymous, 7 In A Barn, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 93)
- Anonymous, Up His Rear, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 93)
- Anonymous, Super Stud, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 93)
- Anonymous, Sailor '69', Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 93)
- Anonymous, One Man's Meat, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 93)
- Anonymous, Navy Discipline, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1970 (Box 93)
- Anonymous, Mr. Harrison's Boarding School, Guild Press (black knight classics), -0-, 1969 (Box 93)
- Anonymous, After Dark, Star Distributors (HardThrobs), HT-142, 1991 (Box 94)
- Anonymous, Garage Studs, Star Distributors (Buddy Books), BB-158, 1988 (Box 94)
- Anonymous, Loving Brothers, Star Distributors, GI-127, 1988 (Box 95)
- Anonymous, Boss Con, Star Distributors, GI-156, 1990 (Box 95)
- Anonymous, Muscle Bound, Masquerade Books, Inc., -0-, 1992 (Box 95)
- Anonymous, Imre, Masquerade Books, Inc., 019-9, 1992 (Box 95)
- Anonymous, Nam Recruit, Star Distributors, CB-113, 1983 (Box 96)
- Anonymous, Slave to His Brother, Star Distributors, BA-124, 1991 (Box 96)
- Anonymous, Dorm Dickmaster, Star Distributors, HD-130, 1991 (Box 96)
- Antholz, Peyson, All Shook Up, Ace Books, D-306, 1958 (Box 1)
- Anthony, George, Homos Don't Cry, Brandon House, 3049, 1968 (Box 12)
- Apollinaire, Guillaume, Memoirs Of A Young Rakehell, Collectors Publications, -0-, 1969 (Box 14)
- Apollinaire, Guillaume, Les Secrets D'un Amoureux Jeune, Jewel Books, 9521, 1967 (Box 33)
- Appleby, Dick, The Reamers, P. E. C., FL 85, 1970 (Box 52)
- Aretino, Pietro, Ragionamenti, Brandon House, 2005, 1966 (Box 12)
- Arthur, Ralph, Coming Out, Blueboy Library, 80092, 1977 (Box 10)